In this material I will tell you about cursor 2, the new version that comes after 1/7.
As you can see, it's introducing composer.
The model is built for low-latency, agentic coding in cursor,
competing most turns in under 40 seconds.
As you can see, the desktop is found a bit little bit quickly with the model we like for,
and we see how it looks like, especially we will be able to use multi-agent interface,
so we can check like composer, tpd codecs, or even more models in the right same time.
But keep that in mind, it will be more expensive.
So even if you have a premium model, you still have to look for the usage right,
because you're using multiple models across the same prompt.
As you can see, the previous model is 1/7, and this one is 2/0.
I'm using Windows, so I will install Windows 64 system,
and then I will press it, or set an English language,
or accessible agreement as well.
And now install in the place, create the desktop icon, and now install.
So basically I use all the default options, except that I just created a shortcut for my desktop.
I will briefly show you what are the differences between the previous model,
because the previous model is like a fork with heroes to your code,
which you can remind you, like whenever you have a hierarchy,
in the middle of the callback code, and on the right,
actually we have something new, because it was an agent.
Now it's more unified, right?
So I just press finish, I will just open it up.
So this is how it looks like.
If you didn't have any application, it might like open like empty,
but this is how the previous model looked like on the left,
we had like a hierarchy.
How is the character maybe like this?
And on the right, we have like an agent.
So here we can type our prompts, and then after that, it will generate a code.
But the other new option would just switch to agents.
So this is the switch to agent.
Here, if you maximize size, it will allow us to switch to agent.
I will not add anything, because I want to create something new.
So here, I'm able to run an agent.
I will be able to use a browser tab, which is actually very great.
So this way I can run it directly.
So the browser tab is in build in the cursor.
So it can open here.
If you choose a Google Chrome, it will open like basically in your own web browser.
I prefer this because it's quickly another option.
We can type voice input if you would like to create something.
And this is such model, it's autumn.
But this is the composer model that I told you about.
You have multiple models, and we can add like multiple.
So if I use max, I will be able to run multiple models.
And I'm using autumn, but still in the premiere, be able to add even your own models.
And create anything that you want.
Here, we just create a new agent, a new agent.
We can switch between plan, which was like implemented maybe two weeks before a new version.
And we can just ask.
So this one, we will just answer the question later to our code base.
But this one, we will plan to create a new website.
So if you want to create a new website or application,
you can start from that because you'd ask you additional questions.
A to me, you're probably just trying to render.
So if you have like embedded points, what are you want to build?
Or you have like a file that you implement in a hierarchy.
Keep that in mind, you can still use the hierarchy in that view.
It will be on the right.
And the toggle panel, especially if you want to use a terminal,
it's great and you can obviously split the terminal,
we can just launch before our expert.
So this one, you can test.
So this one, we just come back to default option that is here.
This one will be allowed to run terminal and run on the hierarchy.
So great, but it's still like it simplifies.
And as you have noticed, actually there is a new update.
And it's quite frequently now because the new version has been released like a few hours ago.
If you press install, it will restore the editor and you will start again.
It's probably contains a few old fixes, but still the main design
and probably the reason you can like that.
And now we're just opening new project and that new project will contain a simple website
that will allow us to use it.
Because you can see it's now updating the cursor.
And now I can just open new folder as a project,
open new window.
But if I open new folder and create just a new project,
I can use watch block.
I'll press a new folder, it will be empty.
So it will not contain any code.
So your code will look like that.
It automatically changed to editor, which is the previous one,
but I want to show a new one.
And I will start from plan.
And first, I want him to create a plan.
So I want to create a block about investing in luxurious watches.
And from here, I will be able to press and run.
Keep that in mind that you can connect the browser.
So this is the browser tab that will allow us to even create it.
But if you want to return to the main tab,
I will just use this and now I will press enter.
So we do plan new moves.
We have a questionable technology tech stack.
Maybe you should like, keep it more simple.
So I think static site is in the better.
So I'll use use static site.
I want to scope for VSO, select seal newsletter sign up.
You can add import for your tools, like affiliate boxes, comparison tables.
I want just posts, text, categories, and newsletter sign up.
And then I will ask for a list of questions that you have provided.
And here we create a plan.
A list that will follow up. And now as we can see, he's creating a plan.
And he will use a structure and files to add and run it.
So we wait a little bit.
We see snippets.
You can even say to build like more static like HTML, JavaScript, and CSS.
But for now, keep it as this, all right.
And now we have like eight to do's that we can see here.
This is the way it will use.
Tailwind next to an operator.
So I press build.
And now it will go directly there.
And follow all the moves to build our block on luxury washing machine.
All right.
So we see already that it has been finished.
So I'll just open it up and there's index HTML.
And if I review, you need a file explorer and open it up, it's not too well.
Keep on the HTML.
I will just simplify it.
So now we'll just quickly change all of it and make it simple.
Because now I have index HTML script.
And as you can see, it has been like mixed up.
So the update quickly design, I will pause the video and then resume whenever I think it's ready.
The website has been created. You have luxury watches, investment insights.
We have a few articles.
Some of them even have images.
Stuck for our images.
We have a filter by a brand that works.
You have a Rolex, Patek, Omega.
Cartier, that's right.
We have a few pages.
But as you can see, you cannot open it up.
And there's even your slider when you can type your email.
Here you can even switch between the hard mode.
That's great.
Especially for the start.
Obviously we can ask another prompt to head another photos to add another
sub pages.
But we start a new project that we look very practical.
And I will guide you how to create them from the very beginning to the very end.